http://www.skeheenarinky.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Introduction
This privacy policy sets out how Skeheenarinky.com uses and protects any information that you give Skeheenarinky.com when you use this website.
Skeheenarinky.com is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
Skeheenarinky.com may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from March 2011.
What information is collected?
We may collect the following information:
name
address
phone number
email address
IP address (what’s this?)
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
internal record keeping
to improve our products and services
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, there are suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures in place to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
Cookies
A cookie is a small text file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
For more information
For more information on data protection and privacy in Ireland, please visit the Data Protection Website. You may also contact us for more information.
